

filip@uxreimagined.com

www.uxreimagined.com

OBJECTIVE

A minimalistic lifestyle, love of jazz and meaningful conversations always reflect in my work. With my background as a chef, a guide and photographer I used to design delightful journeys. Now I design meaningful experiences that inspire and improve people's lives.

EXPERIENCE

User Experience Design student at General Assembly Oct. 2016 – Dec. 2016

A full-time 10-week ux-design program that concentrates on hands-on learning.

Graphic Design & Prototyping Message Modality Dec. 2015 – present

Working as a freelancer on prototype developement, usability testing, graphic design and content strategy for a start up working on a social messaging application.

Fly-fishing Guide – self-employed Jun. 2013 – Sep. 2015

After immigrating to the U.S, I established a small business as a fly fishing guide in the state of Maine. I Provided education and direct customer service to clients wanting to explore remote wilderness areas of Maine.

Spirits of Stone – business owner Mar. 2010 – Dec. 2012

Established a small business importing crystals, gemstones and related products into Australia. Provided high quality products at affordable prices to the local community of various alternative healers and health practitioners in Sydney Australia.

EDUCATION

User Experience Immersive	General Assembly - Seattle	12/2016
Kundalini Yoga Teacher	Guru Gayatri Center - Seattle	5/2016
2 Years of Business	Bridge Business College - Sydney	12/2012

TOOLS

Axure	Adobe XD	Premier Pro
Sketch	Photoshop	Adobe Muse
OmniGraffle	Ilustrator	Git Hub
InVicion	After Effects	Cublima Tayt

